<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>TMS Software</title>
    <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com</link>
    <language>en</language>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2007 22:20:24 +0200</pubDate>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <generator>RSSeditor v0.9.54 (http://www.rss-info.com)</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.tmssoftware.com/tmslogo.png</url>
      <title>TMS Software</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>TMS software updates</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We're pleased to inform about following new updates available from today:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;1) TAdvGlowButton v1.8 : &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advglowbutton"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advglowbutton&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The TAdvGlowButton has been extended with support for notes text in the button. These little helper texts under the button caption can greatly improve the user experience by giving more detail about the function of a button.&lt;BR&gt;Screenshot: &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/advglowbutton.png"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/advglowbutton.png&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;In the latest version, support for C++Builder 2007 has been added as well. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;2) TMS Async32 v1.3.7 : &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?ta32"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?ta32&lt;/A&gt; &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;An update for the lightweight &amp;amp; highspeed serial communications component library is available with support for C++Builder 2007 added and also a new event for TVaTerminal OnDataReceived. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;3) TMS Instrumentation Workshop v1.4.2 : &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tiw"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tiw&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The bundle of over 80 components for building instrumentation software was also updated with support for C++Builder 2007. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS Diagram Studio v2.3 released</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?diagram</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We're excited to announce the release of TMS Diagram Studio v2.3 at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?diagram"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?diagram&lt;/A&gt;. Diagram Studio allows to add diagramming, flowcharting &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;graphing capabilities to your applications. Diagram Studio offers an open architecture to add your own custom diagram blocks. Diagrams can be saved, previewed &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;printed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What's new &amp;amp; improved in v2.3:&lt;BR&gt;- New: Support for C++Builder 2007 added&lt;BR&gt;- New: TatDiagram.ConnectionLineId method allows automatic linkpoint linking&lt;BR&gt;- New: TatDiagram.PageLines property allows to make page lines visible&lt;BR&gt;- New: TatDiagram.AutoPage property allows automatic redimension of diagram area&lt;BR&gt;- New: TLiveDiagram save/load state mechanism. The state of the chart being executed can be saved and retrieved later.&lt;BR&gt;- New: TLiveDiagram execution paths concept &lt;BR&gt;- New: TDiagramControl.MakeVisible method, TatDiagram.MakeControlVisible method - New: PageUp/PageDown key support for scrolling the diagram area. &lt;BR&gt;- New: TDiagramToolbar.ButtonSize property &lt;BR&gt;- New: dbLines in TDiagramToolbarButtons allows to make the diagram toolbar to show only lines&lt;BR&gt;- New: TDiagramToolbar.Mode property (tmObjects, tmConnections). &lt;BR&gt;- New: public methods TDiagramControl.HasDefaultTextCell and TDiagramControl.DefaultTextCell. &lt;BR&gt;- New: TLiveDiagram.OnExecuteEx event.&lt;BR&gt;- New: TLiveDiagram: TDiagramState type dsView shows the current state of live diagram chart &lt;BR&gt;- New: TLiveDiagram.MakeActiveNodeVisible shows the current node being executed in diagram &lt;BR&gt;- New: TLiveDiagram.ViewStateMode property specifies if the start, end or current executed node (block) will be highlighted &lt;BR&gt;- New: live diagram fork block demo &lt;BR&gt;      + Several more new features &amp;amp; improvements&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;A fully functional trial version for Delphi 5,6,7,2005,2006,2007 &amp;amp; C++Builder 5,6,2006,2007 is available now at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?diagram"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?diagram&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Active registered users can obtain the update free after login on our website.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS software updates</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We'd like to inform following updates are available at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com&lt;/A&gt;:&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;TMS Component Pack Pro v4.4 full distribution update Jul 22, 2007:&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Available now with all latest component enhancements and new components for active registered users. A full detail about what's new and improved can be found at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/doc/TMSPCK.TXT"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/doc/TMSPCK.TXT&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;TMS Advanced Toolbars &amp;amp; Menus v2.9.1.0:&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;- New submenu selection in TAdvPreviewMenu design time editor added&lt;BR&gt;Fully functional trial versions are available at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtoolbar"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtoolbar&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Download sample EXE demo&lt;BR&gt;Article on getting started with TMS Advanced ToolBars &amp;amp; Menus&lt;BR&gt;Article on using the new TAdvShapeButton &amp;amp; TAdvPreviewMenu&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;TMS TAdvOutlookList 1.5.0.0:&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;- New : C++Builder 2007 support added&lt;BR&gt;- New : GroupFont property added&lt;BR&gt;- New : GroupCountFont property added&lt;BR&gt;- New : GroupSelectionColor property added&lt;BR&gt;- New : GroupSelectionTextColor property added&lt;BR&gt;- New : GroupColor property added&lt;BR&gt;Fully functional trial versions are available at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advoutlooklist"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advoutlooklist&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;TMS .NET Interop tools pack : TXAMLViewer / TXPSViewer v1.2:&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&amp;nbsp;- Component for Delphi 2006/2007 to make displaying XAML or XPS in Delphi Win32 applications running with .NET 3.0 easy&lt;BR&gt;- Allows Delphi Win32 applications to take advantage of the new exciting WPF features like FlowDocument or 3D capabilities&lt;BR&gt;- Allows Delphi Win32 applications to view XPS files&lt;BR&gt;Fully functional trial versions are available at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?xv"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?xv&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS TAdvTrackBar v2.0 released</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtrackbar</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We're excited to inform about the release of a new component TAdvTrackBar. In response to many requests from users, this is an extensive configurable trackbar component with built-in compatible styles&amp;nbsp;for Office 2003 / Office 2007 color schemes and lots more configuration capabilities to create all kinds of trackbars for multimedia, instrumentation, graphics&amp;nbsp;and many other types of applications.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Screenshot:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/advtrackbar.png"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/advtrackbar.png&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Features:&lt;BR&gt;- Office 2003, 2007 style trackbar&lt;BR&gt;- Includes optional + / - buttons&lt;BR&gt;- Extensive control over appearance&lt;BR&gt;- Gallery with various predefined trackbar styles including capability to add custom style to the gallery&lt;BR&gt;- Fully configurable background, slider, thumb, buttons with extensive color config or customization with images&lt;BR&gt;- Standard or custom drawn tickmarks with support for image tickmarks, rotated text tickmarks etc..&lt;BR&gt;- Configurable slider with appearance for completed / uncompleted part&lt;BR&gt;- Slider is configurable as rating control&lt;BR&gt;- Track hints&lt;BR&gt;- Compatible with TAdvFormStyler&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;A fully functional trial version for TAdvTrackBar v1.0 for Delphi 5,6,7,2005,2006,2007 &amp;amp; C++Builder 5,6,2006,2007 can be obtained from &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtrackbar"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtrackbar&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;The new TAdvTrackBar will also be integrated in the next free full distribution update of the TMS Component Pack (&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspack"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspack&lt;/A&gt;) for active registered users. &lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS TWebUpdate v2.0 released</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?wupdate</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We're happy to inform that TMS TWebUpdate v2.0 was released. With TMS TWebUpdate, you can easily add application executable and/or application data automatic updates via internet or network file transfer to your applications. TMS TWebUpdate offers extensive configuration capabilities to suit your specific needs.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What's new &amp;amp; improved in v2.0:&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;- New : Delphi 2007 &amp;amp; C++Builder 2007 support added&lt;BR&gt;- New : Support for Windows Vista / UAC added&lt;BR&gt;- New : {doc} prefix&lt;BR&gt;- New : support for Hungarian, Czech, Swedish &amp;amp; Polish language added&lt;BR&gt;- New : parameter InitPath added to DoUpdate method to automatically initialize current directory to app EXE&lt;BR&gt;- Improved : logging&lt;BR&gt;- Various smaller improvements &amp;amp; fixes&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Fully functional trial downloads for Delphi 5,6,7,2005,2006,2007 &amp;amp; C++Builder 5,6,2006,2007 are available at : &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?wupdate"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?wupdate&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Active registered users can obtain the free update after login on our website.&lt;BR&gt;TMS TWebUpdate will also be included in the next scheduled full TMS Component Pack (&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspack"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspack&lt;/A&gt;) update &lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New article on persisting column states of TAdvStringGrid</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?asg68</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;FONT face=Verdana size=2&gt;A new article shows how column sizes, column positions, column visibility can be easily persisted with TAdvStringGrid.&lt;/FONT&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New article on Office 2007 ribbon UI button size control is available</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?atbdev9</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;FONT face=Verdana size=2&gt;A&amp;nbsp;new article shows how a developer can have full control on the sizing behavior of buttons in the ribbon UI offered by &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtoolbar"&gt;TMS Advanced ToolBars &amp;amp; Menus&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;BR&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS ASP.NET WebPlanner v2.6 released</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?webplanner</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We're very excited to inform about the release of an extensive update to the TMS ASP.NET WebPlanner. The TMS ASP.NET WebPlanner is a feature-rich first-class&lt;BR&gt;ASP.NET 1.1, 2.0, ASP.NET Ajax compatible component for implementing a broad range of web based planning &amp;amp; scheduling solutions. Whether a project requires the creation of a single-user Personal Information Management (PIM) application or time planning for multiple resources such as hotel rooms, rental cars, and university courses, the WebPlanner provides an open, highly-configurable interface that will suit the project's needs.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Screenshot:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/webplanner1.png"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/webplanner1.png&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;What's new &amp;amp; improved in v2.6:&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;- New: automatic built-in user rights management system via&amp;nbsp;PlannerEvent owner ID, PositionStyle&amp;nbsp;owner ID and user ID / user administrator setting&lt;BR&gt;- New: Methods CreateImageLinkRef, CreateImageHyperlink in PlannerEvent class&lt;BR&gt;- New: Client side events SideBarClick, HeaderClick added&lt;BR&gt;- New: Server side event SideBarClick added&lt;BR&gt;- New: OverlapSpacerWidth property added&lt;BR&gt;- New: PlannerEvent.Caption.Hint property added&lt;BR&gt;- New: CaptionHintStyle Hint type added&lt;BR&gt;- New: EventKey parameter added for client event parameters&lt;BR&gt;- Updated documentation&lt;BR&gt;- Misc: various smaller code improvements &amp;amp; fixes&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;TMS ASP.NET WebPlanner v2.6 is available for Delphi 2005,2006 &amp;amp; Visual Studio .NET 2003,2005. Fully functional trial versions can be downloaded from &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?webplanner"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?webplanner&lt;/A&gt;. Active registered users can obtain the update free after login on our website. &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS Component Pack v4.4 with C++Builder 2007 support released</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspack</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT face=Arial color=#333366&gt;From today, the TMS Component Pack comes also with support for C++Builder 2007. The TMS Component Pack offers over 275 productivity components for creating sophisticated and modern applications faster. An extensive list of components included in the TMS Component Pack can be found at &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspcklist"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?tmspcklist&lt;/A&gt;                       &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;What's new &amp;amp; improved:&lt;BR&gt;- New : C++Builder 2007 support&lt;BR&gt;- Update : Latest TMS Advanced ToolBars &amp;amp; Menus v2.9&lt;BR&gt;- Update : Latest TAdvStringGrid v3.5.4.0&lt;BR&gt;- Update : Latest Planner v2.5.4.1&lt;BR&gt;- Update : Lots of smaller extensions &amp;amp; fixes in various components&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Active registered users can obtain the latest version v4.4 for Delphi 5,6,7,2005,2006,2007 &amp;amp; C++Builder 5,6,2006,2007 free after login on our website. Users with an expired registration are offered an over 40% discount for a full new version cycle (&amp;gt;2 years)&amp;nbsp;of free updates &amp;amp; free priority support. This offer can be found after login on our website. &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;All components that are included in the TMS Component Pack have separate, fully functional and non time limited trial versions on our website. &lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS Advanced ToolBars &amp; Menus v2.9 released</title>
      <link>https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtoolbar</link>
      <author>Bruno Fierens</author>
      <description>&lt;P&gt;We're delighted to announce the release of TMS Advanced ToolBars &amp;amp; Menus v2.9. With TMS Advanced ToolBars &amp;amp; Menus, you can build applications with Office 2003 style toolbars &amp;amp; menus or with the Office 2007 style ribbon interface. &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;What's new &amp;amp; improved:&lt;BR&gt;- New : TAdvToolBarForm, Office 2007 style resizable form with rounded corners, single border&lt;BR&gt;- New : Automatic system font selection support, uses Segoe UI font on Windows Vista&lt;BR&gt;- New : TAdvOfficeStatusBar : Office 2007 style statusbar&lt;BR&gt;- New : TAdvPreviewMenu designer&lt;BR&gt;- New : Extended wizard with generation of application with TAdvPreviewMenu on a TAdvToolBarForm&lt;BR&gt;- New : TAdvPageCaption.MinWidth property added&lt;BR&gt;- New : Exposed DoDropDown method for TAdvCustomToolBarButton&lt;BR&gt;- New : Method MoveUpInRUList added in TAdvToolBar&lt;BR&gt;- Improved : Handling of actions in TAdvPreviewMenu&lt;BR&gt;- Various smaller fixes &amp;amp; improvements &lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Screenshots:&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/atb16.png"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/atb16.png&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/apm.png"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/images/apm.png&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;EXE demo&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/download/TMSToolBarDemo.zip"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/download/TMSToolBarDemo.zip&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Fully functional trial downloads for Delphi 5,6,7,2005,2006,2007 &amp;amp; C++Builder 5,6,2006 are available at : &lt;A href="https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtoolbar"&gt;https://www.tmssoftware.com/go/?advtoolbar&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Active registered users can obtain the update free after login on our website.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>